<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AnimationButtonPlus</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Bella - is not just an alarm clock.\n\n"

        "Do you want to sleep in the morning?"
        "I'll help you to wake up.\n"

        "To wake up cheerful you need to know when to sleep."
        "Our application will help you learn about the phases of sleep and your biorhythms"
        "and also will wake you up at the right time.\n\n"

        "How to work with the application?\n\n"

        "You have launched our application."
        "Animation allows the user to understand that his program does not freeze"
        "and at the same time loads the required functions."
        "There are three buttons on the start screen:\n"

        "- Animation menu button;\n"
        "- Recommendations (Bella Alarm);\n"
        "- Alarm set button.\n\n"

        "By clicking on the animated menu button,"
        "three more options are available on the start screen:\n"

        "- Share App with friends;\n"
        "- Input data about your Birthday;\n"
        "- Graph of biorhythm.\n\n"

        "The logo of the application is placed in the center of the screen, when clicked,"
        "sends the user to the recommendations screen"
        "A large red button (Alarm set button) will send you to the alarm setup screen\n\n"

        "The schedule of biorhythms and mood.\n\n"

        "To view the schedule of biorhythms"
        "you need to enter your date of birth in the format:\n\n"

        "                     MMMM.DD.YYYY\n\n"

        "                     For example:\n"
        "                     August.07.1998\n\n"

        "The biorhythm chart is a collection of three biorhythms:\n\n"
        "- Emotional biorhythm - green graph\n"
        "- Sport biorhythm - black graph\n"
        "- Intellectual biorhythm - white graph\n\n"

        "And also on top of the biorhythms schedule there is a "mood line" that can take 4 values.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "How to share the app with friends?\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Information about the phases of sleep.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">439925716350373</string>
    <string name="show_dialog">Show dialog</string>
    <string name="birthday">YYYY/MM/DD</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="input_your_name_and_birthday">Input your Name and Birthday</string>
    <string name="input">Input</string>
    <string name="inputSuccessful">Input Successful</string>
    <string name="err_msg">Please fill any empty fields</string>
    <string name="this_graph_shows_your_biorhythm_during_the_week">"       This graph shows \n your biorhythm during the \n                    week"</string>
    <string name="don_t_keep_your_device_in_mode_no_sound">"Don\'t keep your device \n  in mode - no sound!"</string>
    <string name="attention">ATTENTION!</string>
    <string name="bella_alarm">" Bella \nAlarm"</string>
    <string name="how_do_you_feel_today">How do you feel today?</string>
    <string name="reload_app_for_look_new_value_into_graph">"Reload app for look \nnew value into graph"</string>

</resources>
